more difficult and different and
difficult approach when you have multi
repositories and agents and you have
agents in separate repository.
Now we will try to kind of simplify a bit
live just to use existing like 2 agents
There.
and we will try to replicate exactly the
same.
Processes which we have in my tube and
uses for for TM.
All right.
Let me.
Yeah.
Someone is not muted.
And it's this.
Can you have it? No, I don't.
Ahh.
Here.
Going to share full screen, so that's why,
uh, give me a second, just...
Really clean up everything.
And I hope we will not have any
interruptions in screen sharing.
All right.
fully from the beginning.
We have TM dot AI, EPAM dot AI,
and there is nothing.
So we don't have anything here at all.
So even releases, so there is no releases.
Currently, if you install.
Sorry, GM Tools, so it will go.
Tur.
This model.
Which is exactly the same as EPAM, so,
and there is, we also don't have nothing,
and ideas that we have agents which are
used in.
In my tube.
And we are going to inject them to GM.ai.
We have already Jira.
Or gem tools which we are going to use,
but the JIRA is not the same,
so actually if you look into workflow.
So, not this one to this one,
so there is less statuses than should be
in the reality,
so we we again probably in production you
will not be able to do this. I mean,
not many projects allow you to to to set
up it, but...
It's simplest way we we need to replicate
the same statuses like we have here,
just to to to make sure that our agents
will be working out of the box, let's see.
So alright, what what I do?
I have superset,
so let's just do everything from scratch.
So I'm creating new project. Let's just.
OK, location, let's choose Gate.
Let's name it GM dot AI. OK,
so we have GM dot AI.
clone so we can clone and we can clone
immediately this one.
Uh, quote, yes, this one.
Probably it will work.
Not sure.
Okay, GM.ai created. I'm using Copilot.
YOLA mod, what model do we have here?
Okay.
I need to run the VPN, yes.
Ohh.
You can ask questions while we're waiting.
Feel free, just interrupt me.
Why do we need VPN now?
Because Copilot does not work without VPN
from Belarus.
And a choice of superset as ID.
Could you remind?
Actually, I don't need ID.
because I don't review the code.
So sometimes, yes, I do,
but I don't need IDE at all, to be honest.
So it's actually not needed.
So I think IDE.
So all IDEs,
even what they do have like intelligent,
Android Studio, so.
I think all of them will will die at some
point, so, because I need this.
And I don't like superset,
just to be honest with you.
I don't like it because, yeah, it's slow.
It's like,
you see all the projects on the left side.
Actually, when I'm working, like...
Several weeks ago,
I did restart my laptop kind of like each
sort day or each few days.
So now I do restart laptop.
So today already three times.
So because I don't know how much space
they have now,
we can even check at the end of the
session. OK, 40 gigabytes. In the morning,
it was 60. I don't know where the space.
So, and I did remove everything.
I mean, like, it just caching, I think,
as it said, nothing else. OK, user switch,
let's just check that we have.
EPAM license.
Let's check model.
Sonic, it's enough.
So we have DMS tools here. Cool.
If you want to install DM tools,
which is actually DM.ai, right?
So you can just write it like.
Help me to configure it.
So, to install skill,
you can go to DM Tools CLEI at current
moment, but we will deploy today, I think,
first release to DM.ai,
and there is you have common line to
install skill, so it's this one.
just install skill. What it does,
it actually just...
Copy the folder,
which is DM Tools AI Docs,
to your Clot or Copilot or Coursor or
whatever else you use.
Clot is supported by everything,
so I mean if you have it in Clot folder,
then it should work out of the box.
So, when you have it, so you see it,
it asks me, like, like in YouTube video,
yeah,
so it asks me what I want to configure,
so, and then, okay, Jira and conference,
for instance, and you see it checked,
so gem tools installed, cool, Java,
not ignore.
No, so actually,
if you don't have TM tools,
so it will help you to install it as well,
and then it's also suggest LLMs,
but actually we'll need Gemini, I think.
So, at some point,
probably I will talk to guys from Audit
the Code Me team, and we will switch.
to do LLM, which is under light LLM.
So I have specific token for this as well.
So we can use, OK, Gemini, for instance.
Gemming is used like there is two types
of agents,
like teammate and test case generator
actually now, and also expert,
and there is more,
but like for reporting purposes,
et cetera, but more common on those. So,
and it it tells you what to do next,
right? So, like base pass, GRML,
GRP token, and instructions what to do.
So, and when you fill it,
so you see that it creates the DM tools.
env, so let me just show here.
It creates one more folder event.
So you have this file.
which is already in Gitignore and it
knows how to communicate to the end tools.
Let me just hide my screen a bit and I
just fills data and you can ask some
questions if you have it.
Or the factory itself.
Do we really need the DM tools dot in?
So actually,
you like when I do run it myself,
I want to test it locally.
So especially if I do run it in for real
customers,
when I have the agent configured,
I can run it locally on my laptop.
to check connectivity, to do LLM,
to co-pilot, to and other stuff.
So usually that helps. That's why, yes.
So it's, I would say,
one of the preferable way.
But in common, probably not.
Is there a chance you can explain your
environment setup?
Tier.
Like the first time I hear the MDM tools
here, right? How these core components?
Work together in your environment.
Give me a second.
Stop.
What do you mean environment setup?
We actually use infrastructure what
customers have.
We use their tracker system,
we use source code repository,
and we use runners.
It can be pipelines in GitLab or runner
workflows, runner sections in GitHub.
or pipelines in Bitbucket or Azure DevOps
pipelines or anything else what they do
have.
Actually some runner which can run some
virtual kind of machine which we
container which we configure.
So DMS tools,
all of this is just local application
which is.
connector to different tools, systems,
let's say, like tracker, source code, etc.
And on top of this, CLEI agents.
So, yeah, agents, what I mean,
like Copilot, Code, Codex, Kiro, whatever,
everything that can be executed in
terminal in headless mode.
Did I answer your question?
No, partially.
Will it be fair to call the DMS tools the
harness within kind of specialized SDLC
harness within the more common harness
like cloud code?
I would not compare it with code,
so it it's not designed for this,
so it's kind of like...
tool which help you to configure
pipelines, workflows, let's say,
with high level of customizations and
pre-built connectors to...
Enterprise systems like Jira,
Azure DevOps, GitHub, Bitbucket, Bitrise,
or Bitrise, no,
so like most of the things which in Figma
as well, so it's main thing.
It's then tools that like doesn't need AI,
let's say.
It can execute some internal prompts for
specific agents like test case generation,
but actually just gives you kind of MCP
for everything, but VSCLEI, not MCP.
To all needed resources.
Thanks.
I'm trying to understand,
besides the connectors that you mentioned,
what's the purpose of these DMS tools?
Is it like,
what is the difference from just command
line?
Uh,
you should watch uh first 10 sessions
from last year.
Or you could try to ask Code Me Assistant.
It contains all the extract.
Mhm.
Is this also that's also possible?
All right.
So.
Actually, what we did,
so I just did copy it,
so it has some prerequisites already,
some connectors to need the tools for me.
So, actually,
I did field DMS tools dot and file,
and what we can do,
we can now just take a new ticket like
this, so from...
We also can use flags like mini,
for instance,
which is give us only short details of
the ticket. And we can, for instance,
like when you connect tokens, et cetera.
So I even can ask also pilot, right?
Give me short overview.
Hold that ticket like this.
And then Copilot also knows how to talk
it.
So like if you want to orchestrate with
Jira, you can also DM tools.
Give me open tickets from TMC Project.
Summary.
And description.
Insurance.
So, in under hood,
you can see that it calls like TM tools,
so now it also again uses TM tools skill
because it's configured. So,
on top of TM tools code base,
it has also access to TM tools
Sí.
infrastructure, let's say Jira, GitHub,
and or everything that is needed. So,
here you can see that, OK,
it will call this JQL.
with mini format so that saves token
tokens.
So actually if you don't need JSONs,
you just use mini format and then outputs
are transformed. So it also search docs,
you see about available tools,
which is like Jira search by JQL, etc.
So you can help your...
agent to orchestrate with your tools if
you just put some instructions.
Just not not ask like me now because it's
not configured to do anything.
So but just.
Preconfigure some rules,
so that means that you can have the rules
for just co-pilot agents, code agents,
etcetera. Yeah, so you see it's got data,
so it can parse,
so the configuration is in place. Alright,
so then we want to connect this one as
sub-repository.
Okay,
so there is some tickets which are open,
by the way, right?
I think all of this which is in review,
it's already done.
I just forgot to close it.
I even can say just move it to done,
by the way. Move the tickets to done.
State,
and let's connect this repository as a
model. OK.
Bull.
So what means next?
When it will be connected,
we need to configure the keys, right?
So if I'm going now to DMS tools.
Main repository, which is already old one,
so to this.
Environment variables, we have secrets,
actions,
and there is keys which are reconfigured.
To do something.
Right, so, and also variables.
which is also again means some co-pilots,
some projects, etc. So first thing,
what we are going to do,
we need to prepare the access to write
your project and all of this. Again,
which keys you need.
So you can chat with system.
If you want to connect Jira,
you need Jira, right? You need Jira email,
Jira IP token.
So if you want to connect Azure DevOps.
You need Adobe personal token and
something else. If you need a Copilot,
so Copilot GitHub token. If you need,
okay, there is also a GCP connection,
so we have GCP keys. In our case,
we don't need it. We don't have GCP setup.
Figma, again, Figma token.
In our use case,
probably we will not need this as well,
but for testing.
In purposes,
it will be needed because we want to
connect full cycle,
so if in future we will modify something
in Figma,
so our tester agent needs to talk to
Figma,
so that's why we will need to provide
some token to allow our test agents to
test it, so here.
variables, some configurations,
which provider we use.
So we are going to use Copilot.
So in this repository,
we support 3 agents.
We support course work on, actually,
as well.
We can also use for test case generation,
and some for here, like it actually.
So,
we also log in and disable it if you have
kind of like for from rest calls, so time.
And then, and yeah, compiler ID,
but sorry, authorization,
so which is not part of the tables.
Over, we barely hear you.
You are interrupting for the last minute
Yeah, I am.
or so.
And now?
Now it's better.
You should get out of your bunker.
I cannot, unfortunately.
All right.
Actually, there is a keys and values.
Because that's clear, I hope.
Right.
Nice.
Yes, it is.
Yeah, it's clear now.
Okay, cool.
But may I interrupt you for a second?
Cool.
Yeah.
Just,
just to summarize what we have already
done,
first you have downloaded DM AI from from
the gate, then you have configured,
you have already had it DM tools as a
skill for for the cursor for the
component, I believe.
Then we're tuning.
for most of them, yeah.
Then we were setting up the connections.
For this example,
it was Jira and Confluence.
And for set up these connections,
we also need to set up keys.
That's what we have done till this moment.
Yes.
Just thank you.
Yeah, cool. Thanks for the summarization.
And there is already some workflows.
And we probably will reuse this partially,
but let's go to our my tool prep.
Yeah, I see my.
Someone raise a hand,
you can ask questions guys.
So interrupt me because I do not look to
chat usually.
If you have it, just Ask.
No.
Okay, then nope. Look,
what we're going to do.
So there is in my tube,
you should configure your workflow.
Actually, the workflow which will execute.
which your teammate will execute.
So what that means,
if your teammate will do development,
it needs to have all environments set up,
like Java, node, tools,
whatever else you use, like keys,
et cetera, you need to set up it.
So, if your teammate needs to,
I don't know,
go to Google Cloud Platform or AWS or
whatever else, again,
it is should be here. So, in our case,
we are going almost copy paste it,
so it is my workflow,
and for each customer, usually it's...
Different.
because different customers have
different things,
but some things can be copied.
So like this.
So usually when we run agent,
we know what exactly the agent is doing.
Like, okay,
story development or solution design or
rework review, automation, et cetera.
So we need this part.
Concurrency key,
it's something that is coming on from
JIRA or from Trigg.
Then it's parameter actually,
then permissions, almost everything.
It's scary. And not really scary for me,
but for most of the people it can be
scary. So kind of.
we allow almost everything.
So then Ubuntu,
if you need Ubuntu or Mac OS,
sometimes Windows,
on Windows it also should work,
at least on Windows Runner.
So on your laptop,
potentially can be some issues.
What then happens,
so we make pre-configured file,
so then we check out repository where we
actually are working with some modules.
Then here we have authentication to
Google Cloud,
we don't need it on our side.
Then we have Java 23 setup. Actually,
DMS tools now works with Java 17,
so we are going to use Java 17 here.
There is some setup workflow,
core source that probably can be removed,
then not we need for a copilot actually,
so nothing else.
And we need not for testing of JavaScript.
So there is we have testing folder and AI
can not here, but in engines.
AI can run some test scripts to test
Graal JS agents. We are not then.
Again, like if you just set up it,
you can skip it,
but I'm trying to also give some overview
what is inside. As there is,
we also give playwright because we needed
to test the MI2.
This website, right? So,
that's why we also, right? Then, yes.
Some value issues again.
Can you hear me?
And not good.
Video is also Stalin.
No.
You crashed your MacBook?
Mm.
I think his bandwidth is too low.
Koriagin. Good joke.
Why are you thinking I'm joking?
What makes you think I'm joking?
Yeah.
Connect Factory.
No, it's the AI I took over his computer.
Mm.
The factory's gone dark.
Collection of collection of the major
jokes regarding the tech factory.
Mm-hmm.
You stole it from my tongue,
dangerous keep permissions.
But...
But perhaps this is connection issues.
But the idea about the AI is very funny.
Your book?
Why are you muted?
Yeah.
Yeah,
there is too many things which my
daughter has, so, but yeah,
I need to alright.
Now, Modem is here, so I can,
I hope you can hear me pretty well.
Burda.
All right.
Yep.
Let's continue.
So, what we are going to do?
We are going to almost copy this.
Like A reference.
Two.
Right.
Ahh.
Okay.
Top.
Clear.
So.
Uh, I need to have...
AI to mate workflow and I want to set up
TM TM tools agents in the repository.
I don't need all the configurations.
I need.
In pools.
Shira.
Long plans.
OK, Azure Dev Ops. OK,
let's add to add all case, then what else?
Figma.
In.
We are going to use Copilot.
And probably that's it.
Chapko.
As well.
And the lids.
He got everything with.
Java 17.
And, for now, we are going to use...
OK, the same installation,
but let's let's go to.
Not the agents, CLEI.
Okay, here,
because we are going to actually...
Test all the time, latest version,
so we need to use main.
Let's use installation of the tools from
main branch.
Sounds like it,
and now it should do the workflow for us,
and after it.
it will create actually all needed keys
and configuration.
And I found a way how to save time for
myself to do all these not really useful
part. So instead of going...
And copy case.
We will ask to write a SAST script.
which will use my DM tools dot N file and
copy secrets and copy variables to to to
to write fields in EPAM DM.
So this is approach which I did found
myself to to simplify life. Unfortunately,
we cannot do a lot of things with Jira.
because of it, but it already can help.
Okay, integrations configured,
we have the file.
I can even open this in intelligent idea.
Like a project, let's close others.
OK.
It's read me, I didn't open. OK, workflow,
yeah, it's it's same part here, right?
And that actually why I'm doing trying to
do a lot of things open source with
different form, because...
When you set up it for different accounts
customers, I need to find a template.
So I know that AI will do it for me and
exactly in the same way if I do provide
template.
So that's why in some cases I just use my
tool as one scenario. I'm just saying,
okay, go to my tool,
check and do the same.
But for this customer with such changes,
or if I need to do something more crazy
with deployments, etcetera, and so on,
we will do it as well, so we can use this,
like I will use my own project which is
closed one, but it has back end,
it has unit test, it has...
integration test Karate,
it has also Flutter, so,
and I can use this like also deployment
workflows, deployments to App Store,
Google Play, like templates. I am saying,
okay, do the same, but with such changes.
And then it really helps me to set up it.
So we have this job info,
cool part token for checkout.
Java 17, so cool, not OK, OK, so.
Copilot.
Good.
Uh...
There is what I do suggest because we
have the agents.
Did the chicken or any agents?
Mm.
Interesting, let's check here.
Oh no, I did not. Okay,
we'll do this later.
Let's ask one more time.
Let's see what else we have.
So installation of Copilot,
what improvements we can do.
So I see that it will install Copilot all
the time,
which is we don't need actually all the
time. So we can say.
We need to install pilot only if the
provider is set in and.
variables.
So, then...
And if you want to use it,
also there is hotkey like control Q,
which is adding your message to queue.
So if you really trust and know that I
can do some stuff, you like can just add,
add,
add new commands and it will do it for
you. So you see it change it.
Then DM tools, it installs from.
OK, DMS tools main main script.
Let's use install from current repo.
Then it's okay, we check in version,
we set up this AI teammate, let's.
Name it like this.
Uhh...
And.
Okay, this is a fine, clear cache true,
cache enable it. Okay,
Azure DevOps for testing,
Figma personal token, blah blah blah. Yes,
we have it, we have it.
Model actually will be set up.
Violet.
If you go variables.
Tools available, fine, prompt.
Silly comments allowed, OK.
And then we do run configuration,
so looks looks fine, alright.
Wanted to check, do we have?
DMS tools release? Yes, we do.
At the 10.
Feel right.
This is such a script which will copy
needed.
Values to secrets.
So, it have Rapaka.
And variables from local team tools dot
and file before.
Execution.
Uhh.
Sure, let me check.
Any questions?
Nothing clear, right? Or, or all is OK.
And.
I'm just trying to replicate the steps
similar in parallel with you and would
like to wonder here you have DMAI,
you have dot GitHub folder,
Ohh, cool.
but there is no DM tool skill inside this
folder.
Yeah,
because this is this is kind of source
here,
so that will be some of the tasks which
Yeah, and.
we will,
you can install them to globally skills.
Yeah, in the M tools, AI docs,
as I saw in the scripts, it checks codecs,
it checks, but it doesn't check copilot.
Yeah, because Copilot used Cloud.
as well.
Okay, I didn't know that. Thank you.
So, yeah, actually, when I did, like,
because first I did design it, like,
if it sees some folders like clot or
co-pilot, etc.,
insert a skill automatically to not all
on this, but then I saw that you have...
two skills in Copilot, one from Claude,
second one from Copilot.
If you install globally, you have three.
So that's why I think we will set up task
for Dark Factory to create kind of script
for installation of skills,
but you will be able to choose what to
install, like skills for Jira.
Skills for Azure DevOps,
because now it just installs all skills.
If you have Azure DevOps,
it or it also will install Jira,
but you don't need Jira in the case, so,
and this is kind of a problem because
usually you do commit it to the code
because agents which are working,
they also need to.
To see the skills as well, right? So,
we have these before executing secret
shows name, source, and key variables,
proceed mapping, configure, Jira, Jira.
Sure, sure, sure, OK.
My bit compiler, JPT menu.
Um...
Scripts setup.
Some GitHub separates. Let's see.
Set up GitHub. Why?
I'm checking this a bit manually because
one time I did run it.
I'm not sure which model I did use,
but I saw my secrets in variables.
So that's why now I'm trying to check it
before I execute it. Otherwise,
I need to go and refresh all my keys.
So and I'm lazy to do this.
All right, looks.
Looks OK.
Uh huh, so compilot model did it in.
Alright, let's execute.
While it's executing, any questions, guys?
OK, nobody sharing the camera.
Everything clear. Alex,
where you are showed.
Do you set up your keys as well or not
yet?
I may ask, who are you asking? Because...
Who is doing this in parallel with me?
It was, it was me, but now I am,
I have rejected,
I have globally installed,
installed damn tools in cloud skill,
but I I don't see it,
so I I now I have it locally in my.
skills in the MAI,
but it is the step on which I am
currently and I am using Windows.
I'm pretty sure that the tools,
Mhm.
I'm not sure, okay,
was it tested on Windows or not?
Uh, it was...
And even we do have kind of test pipeline
for Windows,
and I did install it on my local mini
Windows machine,
but I never use this in production.
Okay.
Sky.
Okay.
because it is a Java.
But, uh...
But, but...
But no, it's not 17 Java, right?
No, no, no, if it requires Java 23,
that means you don't have latest version
of Dentals.
Yeah, yeah, I understood this.
This is why my setup is not yet ready for
the M tools. That's why I'm updating.
Yeah,
you just need to install latest version
Yes.
because, yeah,
at some point I decided to speed up with
JS execution and I migrated to Java 23.
But then in PostNL,
when I did production setup and also on
my local laptop and I needed to test
Android builds, which is usually
running on Java 17,
and then they start to conflict with each
other. So because of the problem,
I decided, okay, I did ask Copilot,
and we just did migration to Java 17.
So actually,
that means that it uses Repnina.
Without acceleration,
but so actually not Graal JS,
but Repnina in the case, or no, no, no,
sorry, Graal JS,
but which is not built in to JDK,
but which is installed like library,
and it's a bit slower than when you have
Java 23.
But, because of on runners,
usually you have Java 17 cached,
so it starts of this is faster, so...
Okay.
So, yeah, I, I'm just updating my setup.
This way I might be, I,
I'm moving slower than you, sorry.
No problem, because that's good.
Uh...
Okay.
At least you are moving.
It says,
so we I did run the execution of updating
scripts and I see that.
My AI teammate does not have access to it,
so that's why I'm going to invite AI
teammate to this repository.
I hope we don't need to go to EPAM
security for this. Let's see if I can.
So at the moment you are not sharing,
it's probably intentional, right,
at this point.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
just want to to to to connect,
let's say this part a bit.
I don't want to share who has access to
the repo.
Uhh...
Okay.
Like this.
Now, I need to accept it.
OK, now it has.
The checkout was not good,
so it has now DM.ai and DM.
ai folders 2 together, so...
Alright, while it's...
Doing the work.
Let me show you a bit.
What we have?
So, we have GM repo, right? Then,
in this repo, we have repository engines,
which is GM tools agents. So,
this part we did not move under EPAM,
but I think in future, at some point,
we will do. So,
my assumption and I think opinion.
In future,
we will have two types of agents.
So this is kind of open source,
which everyone can use,
and we are going to use this for them
tools.
Then we will have custom agents with some
customizations,
what we have already in rituals,
what we I think will have in Primark,
partial in PostNL as well.
Actually, in this case,
you fork the repo and start to customize
it. Why I recommend this approach?
Because in this case,
it covers all the SDLC cycle. So like...
All validation gates, etcetera, etcetera.
Yes, so all of this covered,
so that's why I do recommend to fork it
and then modify, because JavaScript,
so DM tools still is same,
it's executed only,
and the agents are JavaScript and there
is instructions what to do, it takes,
etcetera, right?
So you just fork it and use.
So I do have it like sub repository
because we are going to modify agents if
something will not work.
So actually I did already set up it in
different pipelines,
but I don't know if it is flexible enough
to do our job.
If you need to modify it and customize to
run it, so we will do it.
But better just fork it, et cetera.
Second type of agents will be,
and we will develop it for DMS tools with
Dark Factory. When you have, for instance,
agent like artifact, which is packed. So,
and you can install agent with license.
For example, I have here.
Maestro automation test,
which is I am testing and executing now
in PostNL,
and I see that it is a really cool scene
which I can use in future,
but I will first route,
let's say I will see how it works in
PostNL in real production,
and then I will check, okay, can I apply?
Similar approach in Lauren. If I do,
I will have super smart automation agent
which will use Maestro to test your
Android builds, iOS builds, web builds,
etc. So with right speed,
without horrible Appium JavaScript or
whatever quote it writes,
so it's really horrible.
So, or for example,
you have really cool agent which is
writing react native code with super cool
instructions.
Again, it's your property.
And you will be able to close this,
host it, for example, in GitHub releases,
and then provide license key for your
customers, and while they use DMS tools,
they are able to download the agent,
install it.
Execute, and that's it. If they don't pay,
license explore it, they cannot use it.
So actually,
DMS tools provides this opportunity
already now,
because when I did design this approach,
I expected such easy extensions and that
even in 2024,
I thought that we need to sell agents and
outputs of the tokens in some way.
So that's why it needs to be easy
installed and you can customize it.
So if you talk to some practice like,
I don't know, data practice for instance,
or games, I never did write games,
or I don't know, like.
some unity,
it's also some kind of black box for me,
I never did it. So,
and they develop their own agents and we
can just easy inject it because it's
JavaScript, kind of prehook, posthook,
and some LLM part in the middle.
It can be combination of agents like
Scrum Master.
or it can be report agent which is giving
you report about specific part, etc. Yeah,
so that main idea why it is JavaScript
and Java. So JavaScript is extension.
Java is orchestration level.
Um...
All right, where we are, so...
Cool, all done. It says, like, OK.
I did not want to share this, but I did,
right?
Um...
So, we have separate sets.
Uh, we have variables.
Okay, Azure Devos Project, Rustem.
Organization cool,
so Rustem you should rename it to DM dot
AI already. OK, Copilot DM tools,
Atlassian Copilot model. OK,
now we have money finally, so we can use.
A outs written like this.
By the way,
who knows why Germany family disappeared
from the list?
Do you know?
At some point,
the Gemini models have disappeared from
Copilot.
I really like to use Gemini for some
visual design,
and then I see that it's not here anymore,
and yeah, it's not really nice.
Alright, Copilot cache enabled false.
In this scenario, for local run,
I recommend to enable it for,
but also all Jira data or GitHub data or
whatever, it will be cached.
So you see cache,
cache folder here and actually just
caches this to file.
To to to execute it faster,
but I think we also will redesign this
approach and cache it to some temp folder
in in your repository or not repository
in your system. OK,
Figma basic call transform from tokens
million.
Okay, we don't have Gemini here, right?
Okay, we need it. Let's add it as well.
And.
Let me stop sharing.
Any questions?
Not yet.
Am I right that all what you are doing
right now?
is possible to do locally or not. Oh.
Yes, exactly.
It's actually like locally dmtools.env,
it's your actions variables and action
secrets. It is dmtools.env. And.
Where is it located?
in the root folder of your project where
you do run DMS tools.
So it also can be dot and file as well.
So you place dot and or DM tools dot and
DM tools are read it.
So that's why in post NL folder
repository I do have DM tools for post NL.
in rituals for rituals, for primarking,
for primark, etc. Yes,
so actually it is how it's designed.
So you just create a.
n file as usually you do when you develop
some services, right?
And then you use this.
Secrets and.
For example.
If some of you tell me,
my customer does not allow me to use the
IMS project.
Actually,
that means that you can install Olha.
Locally,
because Olha has cloud models and local
models, or you can install MLX with proxy,
like which is OpenAI compatible,
and use some QAN models for instance,
and you can run locally.
So you can execute DMS tools test cases
generator locally with your local LLMs.
You will not be able to use Copilot,
but for instance,
you will be able to generate test cases.
You will be able to review your current
list of test cases and link related.
So you will be able to...
To write your acceptance criteria as well,
if you use then.
Ah, in Olha,
you can configure even code code to use
Olha.
You can try and use cloud code for
researching in code base,
and then will be CLI mode,
or you can use open code as well,
like CLI orchestrator.
I would say almost each client now is
prepared for AI.
There will be some questions for sure on
VDI,
so on VDI probably will not be able to.
executed so easy, but on your laptops.
You can.
Nobody knows that you do here if you
don't talk to external LLM.
So even if you talk to external LLM,
which is not sharing the data,
so then yes, as well.
So probably possible,
but be careful with this part.
But with local LLMs,
You can. Your experience will be not good.
Probably you will not be able to use your
own laptop during running,
but you can try. So, okay.
We have this setup.
All right.
Mm.
Need and.
So, next, what we are going to do?
Gira setup.
In Jira, let's find something.
I'm not sure, by the way, I maybe I have.
DMC1 - do I have the ticket or not?
No.
Let's see which epics I have.
Okay,
so I need to choose some of epic which I
will use like intake in the case.
Let's imagine that it's brownfield
project. So we have 100 and 101, so.
There is 1 ticket, there is will be a lot.
So that's why let's.
Things there is not a lot of description,
nothing else, nothing here, OK.
This one.
Uh, did-din.
Let's clone it.
It will be our intake.
So something where we will have a role in
common request from anyone.
who is approving this part. Like me,
probably some whitelisted people,
maybe some people who is creating issues
in GitHub.
and the issue is approved and it created
from whitelisted people,
so then we can easily assign it to intake
and then Dark Factory will start to work.
We have this technical container,
let's the previous one renamed. Okay,
cool. Remove clone, it's not needed.
Then we have this ticket,
we need to move it to 850.
Ohh.
Okay, moved.
Now we'll have intake completely.
Clear.
Remo.
So.
Now, we can say...
I have in the ticket.
Then I'm going to say that we are going
to use.
Scrum Master.
From my tube.
Check.
A SM agent.
Was set up.
Sure.
and replicate SM workflow.
In current repo Scrum Master workflow,
it does actually polling model,
so you can use automations.
to get it pretty fast,
like just if ticket moved to state to 6,
so then you will call automation.
It's kind of...
webhook approach, triggers approach, etc.
So because I don't want to pay for Jira
and I want to replace Jira to be honest,
so that's something what we will do also
for our direct factory.
So we do this Scrum Master.
which is kind of each 10 minute,
but it's approximate because GitHub does
not allow to schedule it pretty regularly.
So GitHub decides when to run it,
but we can see that it's still running.
So you see like, yeah, almost each hour,
so it does something.
So,
and if now I create ticket in my top one,
which is intake for my top.
So for example, I want to, I don't know,
there is my videos and for example,
I want to able to manage something else.
I can create a task and.
Scrum Master will be copied and will
develop it without without my involvement
fully, so same approach here.
We want to set up this pipeline,
which is actually what what is doing,
so using part token,
so we don't need GCP here, so okay,
GDK we need all the DMS tools.
And the same credentials,
which is triggering Dmytro Scrum Master
agent.
Like this, which is OK,
let's ask to to run it,
so workflow in current report with
configuration for DMC project.
Um...
So what the agent does?
If you're going to agents, we have SM,
SM agent.
Which is?
Actually, using...
some templates of JQLs and start sessions
locally.
If it does not require any AI logic,
so we just run it locally like TM tools
part, it executes just JSON like PA check,
which is just subtasks.
So if all BA tasks are closed,
so it will move ticket to specific status.
and set label that the agent was
triggered and then be a story analysis,
architecture, some questions,
verifications, all of it.
So our Scrum Master actually does
automation. If we want to do something.
Manually,
you just go to Sales Scrum Master.
and write false.
or true, that's it.
So if you don't allow AI to auto-merge
pull requests,
you need to just disable this agent in
Scrum Master.
What?
Okay, so it's while it's searching,
so we will have it. So in future.
We will design workflow which will pick
up issues from our GM.ai.
So there is one already. I did create it.
Actually, it will pick up it.
If it's created from me,
it will just pick up it.
If it is created from someone else,
it will actually wait for my approve,
for instance,
or for approve from specific people.
When it's approved,
it will create automatically intake
ticket in Jira.
Kirill.
Like a task to start to work on this,
and then we we have all AI.
agents to perform the job and at the end
we'll have pull requests and all what is
needed. So, okay.
And those raised, Sergey, yeah.
Do I understand correctly that you assume
that the initial idea grooming and
backlog grooming happens so far outside
of the main workflow here and it just
starts coming?
It's happening.
It's kind of question answers game.
So if you look to my tube, okay, let's,
for instance,
let's open acceptance feedback.
If I open, OK, there is a box.
Visual design.
If I open any ticket, for example,
this one.
This is your your grooming.
But AI just chatting with each other,
so one AI is asking question.
Mm.
Another AI answering the question.
I see.
So what is the minimal form and what is
the entry point for the absolutely new
feature, for example,
that just came from the product owner?
Just intake ticket, just like this.
You see, intake ticket,
and I just send POC zip,
which is I did wipe code myself,
and say just these two lines of text.
So intake, okay, I actually missed that.
So intake is actually the beginning of
the grooming process.
And then what you said a couple of
Yes, it's kind of like your first point.
minutes ago was about allowing it or not
allowing it to go into the dark factory.
Okay.
Yeah, so, and here you see,
so I did create and take tickets and we
have all train running,
so it creates user stories here or or
bugs or epics and it will link it
properly in in Jira structure,
and so then for it starts to this
critical path as well.
And then it starts to run the agent.
So when the first is ready for
development, so first,
then it start to chatting with each other,
it actually ask answer questions,
then it push a ball to next agent when
all answers provided to write acceptance
criteria. Then like this,
when acceptance criteria are written,
it push a ball to solution architect.
to write solution architecture and next,
next, next, next.
And on each stage you can disable agent.
and say I'm going so I don't want agent
to decide instead of me.
I want to answer questions myself.
So then you just disable agent.
I even would say you should disable agent
to move ticket to done status,
but you should use agent to provide the
answer because you see how detailed it is,
right? So.
When human does it,
usually you will see it like this.
All right.
But agent provides really good answer
with explanation why it is like this.
In some cases it is.
To be honest,
I did not validate it myself.
It probably would be interesting exercise
to check is it different opinion or not.
But also you can set up different models.
So for example,
Sonnet asking questions or Ops asking
questions and Gemini answering this.
or there is no agent,
but we will introduce agent, which will,
I think in Duran, we will play with this.
We will create agent,
which will act as designer.
So,
and the agent will ask design related
questions,
and then Jeremy will answer this,
or maybe we will use even AI Studio and
Nana Banana models to prepare visual
design for vision, how it should work to,
and then another agents will read this as
a reference. So,
We'll think about it because I also want
to connect analytics agent,
which will do an answer in the questions
if needed. We'll use analytics to check,
for instance, user behavior, how it would,
like how it should be, etc. Or each week,
for instance,
The agent needs to check behavior of
users and create intake tickets.
What to do? So, for instance,
I don't see that subscriptions are
growing,
so I don't need to analyze the user flow.
And think about some ideas how to improve
it if Agent TC is the user stacked, right?
And.
Right.
So you're planning to put much more meat
on the bones. As far as I understand,
in all of these deliberative stages,
right,
in the grooming of the ticket and also at
the testing stage,
it is quite important to make sure that
there is less correlation between the
agent, or at least the session creating,
and the agent evaluating, right?
I believe in quote quote.
It's all time clear context.
All the time they have clear context.
If you're about this.
Right, right.
So this is one of the recommendations of
the Cloud Core architects to start with a
clear context, right?
But also you are saying a little bit more
about the different agents,
which is even more kind of reduction of
the correlation between the two,
which is what we want between the tester
and developer. Okay, understood.
And all of the, all, all, all of the...
The skills related to this,
all of the all of the definitions of done,
for example, right,
and style guides and stuff,
stuff like that,
do have a ripper in YouTube.
It's all in my tube.
And.
Yeah, in this repo, them tools agents,
so here instructions, so, for instance,
Okay, thanks.
story questions agent.
Just format like this, so you can combine,
so you can customize it.
There is still a prompt.
prompts here,
actually level of instructions. First,
the top ones is, and then all the rest.
It's not super difficult.
It's like all written with AI with my
short validation, let's say.
Question about.
Yeah, prompt like this, your task, blah,
blah, blah, correct, wrong, critical.
So not big one. And in real production,
there is also new features in DMS tools
where I can create extensions.
So I can actually inherit the logic from
this agent.
and extend only instructions.
That means that you, for instance,
if you want to inject it to your project,
but you don't want really to override all
the agents which are here,
so you just use the agent and you create
your agent and say,
your parent is this one.
and just add instructions and add in your
instructions,
which is in your already commands file or
your cloud MD or agents MD, etc.
So it's kind of extension logic in place
as well.
And you can override if you don't like
this.
action,
so you cannot create subtasks by some
reason, you just override it. And again,
like I did design it,
but I don't remember the format. Sorry.
So I can chat in another chat.
Mhm.
About it, the tools,
how to make a variant of teammate agent
in.
Alright, Jason,
it should be in instructions. OK,
while it's working, we can switch. Good,
it's all here. Let's try.
Amit.
And.
Okay, it will not work. Get it in.
Compare for me my two project setup in
JIRA and DMC project setup if we don't.
Yeah.
Don't have specific statuses.
Create Sam.
You miss the word have, don't have.
Yeah, it's my bad now.
So I'm skipping the words pretty often
and making a lot of mistakes.
But it was interesting part,
if you did watch my last session about
video making, when I did finish it,
I did show it to my wife and my wife said,
why is there so many mistakes in Russian?
So I did read it and for me it was okay,
but she said,
why is there so many mistakes?
And she said,
you need to instruct your agent to write
it without mistakes. So,
and we needed to redefine all text,
but it was pretty fun. Actually.
Probably it's learning from me, so,
and I'm not really good,
good guy in languages, status is create,
create them, OK?
The impulse has also.
Tools to to to to administer Jira,
so that's why potential it will work.
If no, so then no,
if you cannot do something.
Just tell me, and I will manage it myself.
Let me check my agenda for today. Okay,
I will have one more talk.
Right,
you so you see like base agent like this
and then QA,
so it's you can set like pass to base
agent and then say merge or append for
example,
and then you define which parameters to
extend or.
replace or append, et cetera.
So and that how you can customize it.
Yeah,
so there is a merge and there is also
merge. Actually, again, like...
Now you don't hit me and that's what I'm
trying to say is that...
I shifted to more to kind of product
owner for the DM tools, DM.ai.
I have some vision what it needs to do
out of the box,
which allows me to apply it.
Pretty easy for my customers,
and but I don't write the code.
I really trying to to to kind of kill
wrong decisions if it's really breaking
my vision and just guiding it if I do
miss some features. So,
at some point I saw that, okay.
I need these extensions without
overriding my agent,
because if you just need to change one
line,
so why you need to override everything?
So, and I did define the feature,
and I did develop it for me,
so I did test it in PostNL already,
and that works.
That's why, as I'm saying, the agents,
it's free because it's first agents only.
I know all mistakes what they have.
And I know everything how to make it
better,
but I don't have time for it usually.
But that's why it's open source.
And closed agents, which is, let's say,
potentially can be sold via licenses,
which will act like open claw in specific
domains,
but with really good artifacts at the end.
So they should be designed in a really
good way with all practices,
so PE is really good prompting and right
testing approach, etc.
But this is really cool playground.
I mean, like...
I like that I can really pull things
really fast and test it really fast and
so it gives me this opportunity.
All right.
So, you see, actually, what DMS tools did?
OK, so it just checked this API.
Huh, is that it found hack?
It's actually just did use REST API to do
all of the magic,
but DMS also has some tools method for it.
Created, created,
so statuses were created.
I was needs to be manually OK, project.
Strange. OK, let's try.
I did replicate it. Let's let me check it.
And not this one in release.
Mm.
Does it have cloud? No, let's create it.
Well,
let's install latest skill because I
think it uses global one,
which is not up to date.
Ohh.
Damn to silly eye, we have it,
but we don't have skill.
Right.
So I just created clot and you see here,
so it's just created skill.
And now what I can do,
so let's kill the session.
Yeah.
Just check.
Jim, Jim, toes, scale.
And.
Sure, yeah, that's.
How to create statuses?
Is your tights?
You don't have it in skill.
Just search in Jira client.
General class.
First task for DM Factory will be
documentation,
so documentation of DM tools, because,
and Sasha,
who did create this pull request about
Jira Jira skill, Jira DM tool skill,
so potentially we you can migrate it
already to this repository and we can
review it.
Mm.
Any questions?
No.
Let me try to run one button,
what I wanted to do at the beginning.
So actually,
let's create first release in this repo.
Because we configured the keys,
it should be possible to run.
Let's see if it will work. I mean,
release DM tools as DM.ai. Let's see.
Um...
I think we will have next session,
but actually if you do everything correct,
so in next session we will be able
already execute it and maybe I will have
time to do this earlier a bit.
And what we still need is.
guardrails,
so we need to set up unit tests,
we need to protect main branch,
we need to...
Yes, there is already test,
but I don't see unit test here.
So actually some more environment.
If you look to...
Two DMS tools, not DMS tools, my tool.
You can see it.
that we have.
Match trigger, we have out updates,
pull requests, so we have unit tests,
all of this needed.
to organize agents to queue.
What I mean is that at the end,
when pull request is ready,
you must be sure that all the time you
have green tests.
That means that if something is merged,
all other pull requests.
Must be up to date.
So that means that you need to merge main
branch on top of it,
and if there is conflict,
rework agents start to work and fix the
conflict. Without this approach,
your factory will stuck in one, two hours,
because the agents will start break the
code for each other.
And this is one of the prerequisite what
you need to do.
As well.
Greg.
If you have questions, welcome. Ask it.
So try it yourself.
If you can do something,
something does not work,
just let us know in the chat and we will
try to handle next time.
I haven't used Copilot CLI.
Do I understand correctly,
but it is possible to specify which model
I would like to use each time.
Sure, sure.
You just write slash model and specify
the model.
Or you send model as argument to your
headless CLI as well.
And even with DMS tools,
you can specify dot and variable and
And.
specify exact model what you want to use
with Copilot. Let me quickly show you.
I hope guys will wait me a bit to where
it is.
It's pretty stupid, for instance.
And while you are looking to understand
correctly,
that it is possible to use EPAM GitHub
Copilot tokens to perform some activity
in outside repositories outside of EPAM.
repositories.
That's for me, for DM tools, for DM.ai,
for EPAM repository,
I allowed to use EPAM Copilot license.
It was kind of agreement between me and
AI run that I do move it to under EPAM to
AI run.
And they do give me.
Kind of Benefits to use AI models to
support it,
because before I did use my own licenses
to build it and support, so,
and at some point I said, okay,
it's kind of...
I pay a lot for different things and here
it's probably it's okay already to put on
EPAM rails so and that was one of
agreement for your pet projects.
I don't know,
so probably at some point someone will
talk to you and ask why you spent so much
money. But actually, yes, you can.
And here you also can customize
environment variables. For example,
for specific parts,
we can customize model for copilot to use
this one or something else.
Thanks.
Right, guys, need to run. Thank you,
and see you later, then. Bye-bye.